MOAYAD ALMARZOOK

CONTACT INFORMATION:

Phone: +966 547757402

Address: Dammam, Saudi Arabia. Email: moayadalmarzook@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/moayad-almarzook/

GitHub: https://moayadalmarzook.github.io/moayadalmarzook.github.io./

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

Obtained a master's degree in software Engineering from the University of Scranton.. I am skilled in a variety of technologies including React.js, Node.js, Next.js, Java, Graph QL, C++ and Python. as well as structural quarries such as SQL, Mango DB and Oracle. Experienced as a technical support engineer and customer support.

EDUCATION:

Master of Science in Software Engineering, University of Scranton

July 2016 with a GPA of 2.7/4

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, Prince Muhammed Bin Fahd University

May 2011 with a GPA of 3.14 out of 4

EXPERIENCE:

Technical Support Engineer

July 2011-July 2012

- Overseen the ticketing system by assigning it to the fitting involved party. Ensuring the issue is solved and documenting it
- o Supported employees with technical issues onsite and remotely
- o Installed over 100 PCs for classrooms and other educational equipment
- Assisted over 3000 students in installing educational programs and troubleshot general hardware and software technical issues

System Analyst Intern

June 2010 -August 2010

Provided database queries for reports and statistics

Technical Support Engineer Intern

July 2014-September 2014

o Designed an audit reporting system

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Programming languages

- o react native, Java, C++, JavaScript, Python
- o HTML5, CSS
- o SQL, oracle, Mango DB

Integrated development Environment

- o Visual Studio Code
- o Eclipse Spring Boot

HONORS AND AWARDS:

- o King Abdullah Scholarship Program
- o PMU Information Technology dean's list

WORKSHOPS:

- o Education for Employment, Leadership and Communication 2014
- o Basic Leadership and Management Skills 2012

LANGUAGES:

- o Arabic
- o English